American Council for Emigres in the Professions; Records ger017
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP, Undated; 4; originals - 1160 individual files
  - Madelin, Louis, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 192)
  - Maenchen, Otto J., Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 193)
  - Maidl, Francis, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 194)
  - Magat, Michel, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 195)
  - Magnus, Julius, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 196)
  - Mahler, Kurt, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 197)
  - Manasse, Ernst, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 198)
  - Mandelstam, Andrei, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 199)
  - Mankiewicz, Harald, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 200)
  - Mannheim, Hermann, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 201)
  - Mannheim, Karl, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 202)
  - Mantoux, Paul, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 203)
  - Marc, Alexander, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 204)
  - Marcel, Gabriel, Undated (Box 4 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 205)
  - Marcelin, Paul, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 1)
  - Marck, Siegfried, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 2)
  - Maresch, Elizabeth, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 3)
  - Margold, Emmanuel Josef, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 4)
  - Marjolin, Robert, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 5)
  - Markoff, Alexander, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 6)
  - Marrou, Henri-Irennee, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 7)
  - Marx, Jean, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 8)
  - Massignon, Louis, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 9)
  - Masur, Gerhard, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 10)
  - Mattauch, Josef, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 11)
  - Mauss, Marcel, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 12)
  - Mautner, Wilhelm, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 13)
  - Mayer, Alfred, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 14)
  - Mayer, Edmond, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 15)
  - Mayer, Gustav, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 16)
  - Mayer, Hans, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 17)
  - Mayer, Melanie, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 18)
  - Mayer, Richard, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 19)
  - Mazzuchetti, Lavinia, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 20)
  - Meijers, E. M., Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 21)
  - Meinhard, Heinrich, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 22)
  - Meisel, James, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 23)
  - Meitner, Clarisse, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 24)
  - Meitner, Lise, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 25)
  - Melese, Pierre, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 26)
  - Mendelssohn, Thomas, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 27)
  - Menges, Karl, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 28)
  - Mengin, Robert, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 29)
  - Mennicke, Carl, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 30)
  - Menzio, Francesco, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 31)
  - Mering, Jacques, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 32)
  - Merkel, George, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 33)
  - Merlean, Ponty, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 34)
  - Mesnard, Pierre, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 35)
  - Mestitz, Franz, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 36)
  - Metall, Rudolf, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 37)
  - Metalnikov, Sergei, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 38)
  - Meusel, Alfred, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 39)
  - Meyer, Gerhard Emil, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 40)
  - Meyer, Lothar, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 41)
  - Meyerhof, Heinz, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 42)
  - Meyer-Lindenberg, Hermann, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 43)
  - Meyerson, Ignace, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 44)
  - Meyler, L., Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 45)
  - Michael, Franz, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 46)
  - Michelson, Alexander, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 47)
  - Michotte, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 48)
  - Mila, Umberto, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 49)
  - Milano, Paolo, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 50)
  - Milbauer, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 51)
  - Minder, Robert, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 52)
  - Minkowski, Eugene, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 53)
  - Mintz, Alexander, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 54)
  - Mira, Emilio, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 55)
  - Misch, Georg, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 56)
  - Missong, Alfred, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 57)
  - Mockrauer, Franz, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 58)
  - Modona, Alfo, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 59)
  - Moholy-Nagy, Sibyl, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 60)
  - Momigliano, Arnoldo, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 61)
  - Momigliano, Attilio, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 62)
  - Mopurgo, Giorgio, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 63)
  - Morgenstern, Otto, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 64)
  - Moricard, Rene, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 65)
  - Moritz, Manfred, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 66)
  - Morpurgo, Beno, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 67)
  - Mortara, Giorgio, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 68)
  - Mosse, Walter, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 69)
  - Mossner, F., Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 70)
  - Mostny, Grete, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 71)
  - Mounier, Emmanuel, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 72)
  - Mueller, Hugo, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 73)
  - Muir, Edwin & Willa, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 74)
  - Mühsam, Alice, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 75)
  - Munthe, Wilhelm, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 76)
  - Musatti, Cesare, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 77)
  - Musil, Robert, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 78)
  - Myslivec, V., Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 79)
  - Nadel, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 80)
  - Nandris, Grigori, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 81)
  - Neppi-Modona, Aldo, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 82)
  - Neugebauer, Otto, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 83)
  - Neumann, Sigmund, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 84)
  - Neumark, Fritz, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 85)
  - Neurath, Otto, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 86)
  - Neustadt, Ernst, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 87)
  - Nevanlinna, Rolf, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 88)
  - Nevanlinne, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 89)
  - Nicolau, Luis, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 90)
  - Niklewski, B. K., Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 91)
  - Noether, Fritz, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 92)
  - Nolde, Boris Baron, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 93)
  - Nouneberg, Louta, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 94)
  - Odinetz, Dmitri, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 95)
  - Oettinger, Walter, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 96)
  - Oguze, Andre, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 97)
  - Okunev, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 98)
  - Olbrechts, Frans, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 99)
  - Olden, Rudolf, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 100)
  - Oljenick, Ignaz, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 101)
  - Olschki, Leonardo, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 102)
  - d'Olwer, Luis Nicolau, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 103)
  - Oppenbeini, E., Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 104)
  - Oppenheim, Adolf Leo, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 105)
  - Oppenheim, David Ernst, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 106)
  - Opresco, Georges, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 107)
  - Ording, Arne, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 108)
  - Ornstein, Leonard Salomon, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 109)
  - Ostrogorsky, George E., Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 110)
  - Ostrovsky, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 111)
  - Ostrowski, Stanislaw, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 112)
  - Ottemberg, Robert, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 113)
  - Ougrimoff, Alexander, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 114)
  - Overbeek de Meijer, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 115)
  - Paneth, Erwin, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 116)
  - Papp, Desiderius, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 117)
  - Paraz, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 118)
  - Partos, Paul, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 119)
  - Pegna, Ubaldo Lopes, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 120)
  - Perels, Leopold, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 121)
  - Perez, Jose Simon, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 122)
  - Perez, Victoria Augusto, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 123)
  - Perl, Walter, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 124)
  - Perlitz, Harold, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 125)
  - Pernot, Huber, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 126)
  - Perrin, Francis, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 127)
  - Perroux, Francois, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 128)
  - Perutz, Max F., Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 129)
  - Petersen, Lothar, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 130)
  - Petit, Juan, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 131)
  - Pevsner, Nikolaus, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 132)
  - Pfeiffer, H., Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 133)
  - Pfleiderer, Otto, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 134)
  - Philip, Andre, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 135)
  - Philippson, Alfred, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 136)
  - Piaget, Josef, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 137)
  - Piatier, Andre, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 138)
  - Piccard, Jean, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 139)
  - Pick, Otto, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 140)
  - Pick, Georg Siegmund, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 141)
  - Pieron, Henri, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 142)
  - Pierre, Andre, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 143)
  - Pikler, Endre, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 144)
  - Pincherle, Alberto, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 145)
  - Pirani, Marcello Stefano, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 146)
  - Pirou, Gaetan, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 147)
  - Pizarro, Miguel, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 148)
  - Plaut, Theodore, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 149)
  - Plessner, Helmuth, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 150)
  - Plewa, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 151)
  - Ploechl, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 152)
  - Polak, Bettina Henriette, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 153)
  - Polak, Leonard, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 154)
  - Policer, Geza, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 155)
  - Pollaczek, Felix, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 156)
  - Pollak, Leo, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 157)
  - Pollog, Carl Hanns, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 158)
  - Porada, Edith von, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 159)
  - Pordes, Fritz, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 160)
  - Pos, Hendrik J., Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 161)
  - Pradines, Maurice, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 162)
  - Prijs, Joseph, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 163)
  - Pringsheim, Fritz, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 164)
  - Pringsheim, Peter, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 165)
  - Prinzheim, Nitemeo, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 166)
  - Przeworski, Stefan, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 167)
  - Przibram, Hans, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 168)
  - Przibram, Karl, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 169)
  - Przychocki, Gustav, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 170)
  - Pulewka, Paul, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 171)
  - Quesnel, Georges, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 172)
  - Quigley, Hugh, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 173)
  - Quint, Pierre, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 174)
  - Raalte, Ernest van, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 175)
  - Rado, Alexander, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 176)
  - Radvany, Ladislav, Undated (Box 5 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 177)
  - Rahmer, B. A., Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 1)
  - Raknes, Ola, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 2)
  - Ranuff, Svend, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 3)
  - Raphael, Max, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 4)
  - Rapp, Franz, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 5)
  - Rappaport, Philipp A., Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 6)
  - Ratnasuriya, M. D., Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 7)
  - Reale, Egidio, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 8)
  - Redlich, Otto, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 9)
  - Redslob, Robert, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 10)
  - Reich, Hans, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 11)
  - Reichardt, Konstantin, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 12)
  - Reinemann, Otto, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 13)
  - Reiwald, Paul, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 14)
  - Remizov-Dovgelo, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 15)
  - Renaudet, Augustin, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 16)
  - Reuss, Frederick, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 17)
  - Reuter, Herr, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 18)
  - Revesz, Geza, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 19)
  - Revesz, Judith, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 20)
  - Rey, Abel, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 21)
  - Rheinstrom, Heinrich, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 22)
  - Ricci, Umberto, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 23)
  - Riesenfeld, Albert, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 24)
  - Riesz, Eugen, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 25)
  - Rintelen, Captain von, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 26)
  - Rivet, Paul, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 27)
  - Rochmis, Theodore, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 28)
  - Rodriquez, Mata Enrique, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 29)
  - Roepke, Wilhelm, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 30)
  - Romein, Jan M., Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 31)
  - Roos, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 32)
  - Rops, Daniel, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 33)
  - Rosenblum, Salomon, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 34)
  - Rosenfeld, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 35)
  - Rosenstein-Rodan, P.N., Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 36)
  - Rosenthal, Friedrich, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 37)
  - Rosenthal, Helmut, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 38)
  - Rossi, Mario, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 39)
  - Rostas, Laszlo, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 40)
  - Rothbart, Erwin, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 41)
  - Rothbarth, Margaret, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 42)
  - Rothberger, Fritz, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 43)
  - Rothe, Hans, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 44)
  - Rothfels, Hans, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 45)
  - Rouai, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 46)
  - Rubin, Edgar, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 47)
  - Ruedenberg, Werner, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 48)
  - Rueff, Jaques, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 49)
  - Rüstow, Alexander, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 50)
  - Sadowsky, Michael A., Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 51)
  - Saenger, August, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 52)
  - Saks, Stanislaw, Undated (Box 6 (4-Files from Else Staudinger, Director of ACEP), Folder 53)